Tejas Kumar Dadhaniya

SUMMARY

A passionate data science enthusiast having knowledge data processing, EDA, data mining algorithms and forecasting to solve challenging business problems. Strong background in Python, hands on experience of supervised and unsupervised machine learning approach and knowledge of Deep learning techniques.

EXPERIENCE

COMPUTER VISION INTERN

iNeuron.ai, Bengaluru | May 2021 - Present

- Collected image data and performed annotation.
- Build face mask detection model using SSD mobilenet, and Centernet mobilenet.
- Created workflow for model building.

DATA SCIENCE AND BUSINESS ANALYTICS INTERN

The Sparks Foundation | May 2021 - June 2021

- Analyzed and performed EDA on given dataset
- Created dashboard using python and dash.
- evaluated peer's task.

PROJECTS

I-ML (Ongoing)

- I-ML is web application used for developing end to end machine learning project.
- **Key features** Automatic data pre-processing, model selection, logging, dashboarding, cloud storage integration, database integration (MongoDB atlas) etc.

WATER QUALITY CHECKER

- Water quality checker is web application created using flask and python to check quality of water based on input parameters.
- **Tools** & **Libraries** python, flask, sklearn, pandas, GitHub, CI/CD pipeline, Heroku
- Source code https://github.com/Tejas2512/WaterQuality
- App URL https://water-potability-checker.herokuapp.com/

FITNESS CHECKER

- To build a regression model to predict the calories burnt based on the given indicators in the training data.
- Automate machine learning cycle.
- Model selection to find best model having good r2 score to perform predictions.
- **Tools** & **Libraries** Python, MongoDB atlas, Azure storage, Docker, sklearn, pandas, Flask, Git
- GitHub https://github.com/Tejas2512/fitbit

CREDIT CARD DEFAULTERS

- To build a classification methodology to determine whether a person defaults the credit card payment for the next month.
- **Libraries** Python, MongoDB atlas, GCP storage, sklearn, pandas, Flask, Git
- GitHub https://github.com/Tejas2512/CreditCardDefaulters

- +91 95860 27824
- https://github.com/Tejas2512
- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/tej as-dadhaniva-a445221b0/
- https://inblog.in/@dadhaniya tejas

KEY SKILLS

Python programming Machine Learning

Deep learning

Object detection

Model building

Data cleaning

Data preprocessing

Statistics

TECHNICAL SKILLS

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

– Pvthon

DATABASE

- MongoDB, MySQL

FRAMEWORK

- TFOD, Darknet

LIBRARIES

TensorFlow, Keras,
sklearn, pandas, Flask, plotly,
dash, NumPy, seaborn,
matplotlib etc.

TOOLS

Docker(basic), GitHub

EDUCATION

M.Sc. | Physics

Sardar Vallabhbhai National Institute of Technology, Surat 2015 – 2020 CGPA – 7.96/10

CERTIFICATION

Machine Learning Masters

iNeuron

AUG 2020 - APR 2021